baldwinfilter.com 2018-12-15

# Baldwin Filters | Privacy Policy

Baldwin Filters is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. 

Baldwin Filters may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time. This policy is effective from June 25, 2012. 

The information we may gather may be used to improve our products and services.

We will not provide your information to third party partners and we will never sell your information.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you individually. We may utilize this data to identify your company, and it is possible that a sales representative may contact your company in the future. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links that enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites, which are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at clarcoremg.info@clarcor.com. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law.
